<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kamminga, J.J.</title>
    <link>https://agitated-curran-41fd3b.netlify.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kamminga, J.J.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 22:22:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://agitated-curran-41fd3b.netlify.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Most listened 2019</title>
      <link>https://agitated-curran-41fd3b.netlify.com/blog/mostlistened2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 22:22:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agitated-curran-41fd3b.netlify.com/blog/mostlistened2019/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m always interested in the music that&amp;rsquo;s the best to come out in any given year, but this often contrasts heavily with my actual listening habits. This is why I look to Last.fm for my top listened to albums of the year.
 Flume - Hi This Is Flume Flying Lotus - Flamagra Denzel Curry - Zuu Weval - The Weight Vorna - Sateet palata saavat Sensible Soccers - Aurora Behemoth - I Loved You At Your Darkest Borknagar - True North Yagya - Stormur James Blake - Assume Form  For reference, my albums of the year 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOTY2019</title>
      <link>https://agitated-curran-41fd3b.netlify.com/blog/soty2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 22:15:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agitated-curran-41fd3b.netlify.com/blog/soty2019/</guid>
      <description>Along with my album of the year, the last few years I have been posting about my top songs of the year as well. Well, I&amp;rsquo;ll stop talking because these songs speak for themselves!
Note that they are sorted for listenability more than for any actual order.
You can also find this list as a playlist on Spotify!
   Artist Song     Rammstein DEUTSCHLAND   James Blake I&amp;rsquo;ll Come Too   Leprous Distant Bells   Flying Lotus &amp;amp; Denzel Curry Black Balloons Reprise   Hot Chip Hungry Child   Vorna Virvatulet   Borknagar Up North   Yugen Blakrok Land of Gray   James Blake Don&amp;rsquo;t Miss It   Alcest Le Miroir    Please let me know what you think!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AOTY2019</title>
      <link>https://agitated-curran-41fd3b.netlify.com/blog/aoty2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 21:41:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agitated-curran-41fd3b.netlify.com/blog/aoty2019/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the time of year where I talk about way more than anyone is willing to care about&amp;hellip; the ALBUM OF THE YEAR.
I keep track all year, every year, and 2019 has been no different. Like 2018, it&amp;rsquo;s been a year without any huge instant classics, but lots of good quality in lots of different genres. I had an easy time picking 20 contestants for this list, but a very hard time arranging them and making the final cut.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOTY2019</title>
      <link>https://agitated-curran-41fd3b.netlify.com/music/soty2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 14:41:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agitated-curran-41fd3b.netlify.com/music/soty2019/</guid>
      <description>   Artist Song     Rammstein DEUTSCHLAND   James Blake I&amp;rsquo;ll Come Too   Leprous Distant Bells   Flying Lotus &amp;amp; Denzel Curry Black Balloons Reprise   Hot Chip Hungry Child   Vorna Virvatulet   Borknagar Up North   Yugen Blakrok Land of Gray   James Blake Don&amp;rsquo;t Miss It   Alcest Le Miroir    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Solitaire</title>
      <link>https://agitated-curran-41fd3b.netlify.com/stories/the-solitaire/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 15:57:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agitated-curran-41fd3b.netlify.com/stories/the-solitaire/</guid>
      <description>How long had I walked? I cannot say with precision. But many hours had passed since I was last able to see more than a hundred yards, through trees so dense that sometimes I could not even see the river I followed. Part of me was glad to be able to walk again, and breathe the air of the forest. I had been on a ship from Dantes across the bay, and then taken the long journey up the river Marnix to the border.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post on My New Website!</title>
      <link>https://agitated-curran-41fd3b.netlify.com/blog/first-post-on-new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 09:41:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agitated-curran-41fd3b.netlify.com/blog/first-post-on-new-website/</guid>
      <description>Hooray! This post marks the start of my blogging adventure on my brand new, self created website.
This blog is going to be about all kinds of things. Whatever I feel like writing about, honestly, but there will be some major themes: web development, music, and just some personal thoughts about&amp;hellip; well, not sure about what yet! I may also fill up an archive of blogposts from my previous site. But for now, please have a look around and let me know if you like it!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>